(Leonard:)Sheldon, why?
(Sheldon:)You see, while Leo would not
have gone into rehab...
(Sheldon:)...it is completely plausible that we would
have talked him into leaving the motel...
(Sheldon:)- ...and coming home with us.
- Oh...
(Toby:)Sheldon, how about this
as my motivation?
When I was 14 years old...
(Toby:)...I was abused in the Philippines
by a clubfooted Navy chaplain.
(Sheldon:)No, we're going with middle child
and a genetic predisposition...
(Sheldon:)...to inadequate serotonin production.
Swell, well, how do I play
genetic predisposition?
(Sheldon:)Subtextually, of course.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Sheldon:)Just have fun with it.
- Morning, Penny.
- Hi. How did the intervention go?
(Sheldon:)Unfortunately, we weren't able
to convince him to go to rehab.
(Penny:)Well, based on what you told me,
I'm not surprised.
(Sheldon:)But we did convince him
to leave the motel.
(Sheldon:)Come say hello.